Guide to the Arthur Brown Papers SC0707
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Arthur Brown papers
1910-1961
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Brown, Arthur
SC0707
22 Linear Feet
The papers of Arthur Brown, Jr. include correspondence, professional papers, clippings, and architectural drawings, pertaining to Hoover Tower and other buildings designed for Stanford University.
Biographical/Historical note
Arthur Brown, Jr. and John Bakewell, Jr. formed their San Francisco architectural firm, Bakewell and Brown, in 1906. They became associated with Stanford University in 1913. They designed a number of campus buildings, including the education building, art gallery, library (1919), Hoover tower, women's gymnasium, and several dormitories.
Scope and Contents note
The papers of Arthur Brown, Jr. include correspondence, professional papers, clippings, and architectural drawings, pertaining to Hoover Tower and other buildings designed for Stanford University. The correspondence dates from 1923-61 and largely pertains to the design and construction of Hoover Tower, including the carillon bells. Correspondents include Ray Lyman Wilbur, Ralph H. Lutz, Herbert Hoover, Hunter and Hudson (consulting engineers), F. E. Terman (re installation of radio antennae on the tower), Clifford M. Swan (acoustical engineer), and Frank F. Walker. The correspondence file labeled "Stanford Question," 1929-39 pertains to Brown's dispute with Bakewell and Weihe on responsibility for work at Stanford and use of corporate names. Also included in the correspondence are letters from Herbert Hoover to Mrs. Brown after Arthur Brown's death, 1957-61. The professional papers include drawings, notes, reports, and photographs pertaining to Stanford buildings, including Hoover Tower, the education building, and proposed law and chemistry buildings. The architectural drawings and specifications date from 1916-41, with many drawings undated; Stanford buildings include Hoover Tower, Memorial Auditorium, education building, library, dormitories, Encina Gym, Home for Convalescent Children, and proposed law quad and dormitories. There are also drawings and specifications for a new wing at the Stanford Hospital in San Francisco.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Separated Materials note
The following items were removed from the Arthur Brown Papers during processing and added to the Stanford University Archives Architectural Drawings collection: 1. Blueprint: Large Dormitory No. 2, Front Elevation, Shepley, Rutan & Coolidge (stored under number 06-010); 2. Blueprint: History Corner, South Elevation, C. E. Hodges [printed in reverse] (stored under number 01-200); 3. Blueprint: Natural Sciences Building, North Elevation, Henry A. Schulze, 1899 [signed by Charles Lathrop 1901] (stored under number 01-120 / 01-160).
Architecture -- California.; Architectural drawings.; Brown, Arthur; Brown, Arthur; Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace; Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace; Bakewell and Brown; Wilbur, Ray L. (Ray Lyman); Walker, Frank Fish; Terman, Frederick Emmons, 1900-1982; Lutz, Ralph Haswell; Swan, Clifford M.; Hoover, Herbert
- Papers, Series 1
  - Correspondence, 1923-1961; Subseries 1
    - Correspondence, 1923-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1940 Jan-Mar (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1940 Apr-Aug (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1940 Sep-Oct (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1940 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1941 Jan (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1941 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1941 Apr-May (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1941 Jun-Jul (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1941 Aug-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1942-1945, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence with Frank Walker, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence on "Stanford Question", 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, personal, 1937-1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, drafts of letters to H. Hoover, 1952 and undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Herbert Hoover to Mrs. Brown, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Greeting cards and postcards (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Professional Papers, 1914-1951; Subseries 2
    - Bakewell & Brown ads featuring Stanford buildings (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bakewell & Brown, Stanford plans (photographic reproductions), 1914, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Chemistry building, Stanford, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Education building, Stanford, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Hoover Tower, original scheme and estimate, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hoover Tower, correspondence and drawings, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Hoover Tower, designs, memos, correspondence, notes, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Hoover Library, costs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Hoover Library, notes, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Hoover carillon, photographs and notes (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Hoover Tower, text for Commission for Relief in Belgium plaque (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Hoover Tower, dedication, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Memo on computing stack capacity in terms of volumes (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Law building, Stanford, requirements, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University cost data (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Stanford general plan, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Stanford photographs, mostly pertaining to Bakewell & Brown buildings, late 1930s-early 1940s (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Stanford report, data and correspondence, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Stanford, miscellany and ephemera (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - "Carillons at Christmas," holiday booklet put out by Hermann Safe Company, San Francisco, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Gladding, McBean & Co., "Shapes of Clay", 1926 Aug (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Drawings, miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, Subseries 3
    - Herbert Hoover (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Herbert Hoover's 75th birthday, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Herbert Hoover, birthday speech of 1951 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Hoover / MacArthur, GOP, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Herbert Hoover Jr. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Stanford, Hoover Tower, etc. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Publications, 1940-1945; Subseries 4
    - Mumford, Lewis, "The School of Humanities at Stanford", circa 1945 (Box 2)
    - Laroza, Enrique, "Observations on my visit to some Educational Institutions of the United States", 1943 (Box 2)
    - The Hoover Library on War, Revolution, and Peace, Annual Report of the Chairman, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - Oversize Materials, Subseries 5
    - Preliminary studies for Law Group at Stanford University, Bakewell & Brown (2 items), 1938 (Box 3)
    - Ink and watercolor elevation of a church, Bakewell & Brown, 1925 Jun 24 (Box 3)
    - Photo of Bakewell & Brown elevation of a dorm group, 1921 Jul 25 (Box 3)
    - Photos of Bakewell & Brown "Plan of Existing and Proposed Buildings, Stanford University", 1920 Aug (Box 3)
    - Aerial photo of Stanford (after Memorial Hall but before Hoover Tower) (Box 3)
    - Two pages of printed images of Stanford men's dormitory interiors (Box 3)
    - Blueprint, additions to dining room, Stanford Union building, 1938 (Box 3)
    - Pencil drawing of Hoover Tower (mounted on board), signed "AB Mar. 25 1939" (Box 3)
    - Assorted drawings (blueprint and others) mostly of Hoover Tower (Box 3)
    - Assorted drawings on tissue, 1924-1939, including Memorial Auditorium, 1937, Art Gallery/Memorial Hall, 1937, Typical Stack floor Hoover Tower, 1939, floor plans Hoover Tower, 1927-39, and many sketches of tower shapes (Box 3)
    - Photo of Hoover Tower model (Box 3)
    - Three elevations of Hoover Tower on one sheet (2 copies) (Box 3)
    - Mounted photo of Hoover Tower, prior to landscaping, 1940 (Box 3)
    - Copy of the Shepley, Rutan & Coolidge / Olmsted print of The Leland Stanford Jr. University [same as SUA print P001] (Box 3)
    - Blueprint of Hoover Tower stack scheme (Box 3)
    - Print labeled Stanford University of the Present and of the Immediate Future (Crandall aerial image) [same as SUA print P019], 1922 (Box 3)
    - Bakewell & Brown Proposed Hoover Library - War Memorial and Law School Group (mounted on board), 1925 (Box 3)
    - Stanford Law Group drawing, 1925 (Box 4)
    - Education Building and Memorial Auditorium drawing, 1937 (Box 4)
    - Chemistry annex drawing, 1941 (Box 4)
    - Proposed Clinic building drawing, Stanford Hospital, San Francisco (Box 4)
    - Stanford planning, Quad II drawing, 1937 (Box 4)
    - Freshmen's residence hall drawing, 1941 (Box 4)
    - Hoover Library, lobby and exhibition room details drawing 1940 (Box 4)
    - Galvez street elevation [a dorm plan?] [several drawings, including Serra Street elevation with Memorial Arch intact], 1941 (Box 4)
    - Hoover Tower elevations (Box 4)
    - Stanford steam conduit drawing (Box 4)
    - Toyon & Branner dorm complex drawing, 1922 (Box 4)
    - Stanford Quad II schematic sketches (Box 4)
    - Hoover Tower, 1st and 2nd floor plans, original (Box 4)
    - Hoover Tower blueprints (Box 4)
    - Stanford Law Group plan, 1937 (Box 4)
    - Stanford Library and School of Education, Lasuen Street elevation (Box 4)
    - Hoover Tower, north elevation, blueprint, circa 1940 (Box 4)
    - Sketches of proposed residence hall for Stanford University, Bakewell & Brown (2 items), 1922 Jul (Item 1)
    - Hoover Tower elevator inscriptions, Bakewell & Brown, 1941 Feb (Item 1)
    - Inscription over elevator door, lobby of Hoover Tower, Bakewell & Brown, 1941 Feb (Item 1)
    - Hoover Tower proposed landscape treatment, Bakewell & Brown, 1940 Mar 14 (Item 1)
    - Print: sketch of proposed Hoover Tower by Francis Todhunter (Item 1)
    - Stanford bird's eye, old Quad [Shepley, Rutan & Coolidge design] with adaptation by Bakewell & Brown showing new library west of the Quad [compare to SUA Print P001a], 1916 (Item 2)
    - Stanford Campus - general plan, focus on roads, blueprint (2 cc), 1921 (Oversize 1)
    - Stanford Quad II Base Map [shows location of 1919 library] (Oversize 1)
    - Stanford Aerial Map [schematic of building placement], circa 1940 (Oversize 1)
    - Hoover Library - large scale [multiple drawings] (Oversize 1)
    - Stanford residence hall plans, 1922 (Oversize 1)
    - Stanford General Plan (showing additions to 1919 library and other new structures), original pencil and blueprint copy, 1941 (Oversize 1)
    - V14 Stanford University Hospital New Wing - architectural (Oversize 1)
    - V15 Stanford University Hospital New Wing - structural (Oversize 1)
    - V16 Stanford University Hospital New Wing - F.S.D. (Oversize 1)
    - V17 Stanford University Hospital New Wing - electrical and mechanical (Oversize 1)
- Additional Drawings, Accession ARCH-2006-256
  - Apartment house, specifications, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Entrance Gates, specifications, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Home for Convalescent Children, Third Unit, Women’s Auxiliary Board Unit, specifications, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Home for Convalescent Children, original plus additions, specifications, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Home for Convalescent Children, Gates, specifications, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hoover War Library, specifications, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Hoover War Library, memoranda on costs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lagunita Court, specifications, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lagunita Court, additions, specifications, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lagunita Court, clipping about steel frame, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lane Medical, San Francisco, laboratory building additions, specifications, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Loeb Laboratory, HMS, Pacific Grove, specifications, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - School of Education, specifications general, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - School of Education, specifications electrical, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - School of Education, specifications heating, ventilation, plumbing, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Hospital additions, San Francisco, specifications, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Memorial Hall, specifications general, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Hall, specifications heating, plumbing, electric, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - School of Nursing, San Francisco, photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University miscellaneous: correspondence and a copy of The Yale Alumni Weekly (Memorial Quadrangle Number), 1921-1931 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University photographs, including Crothers Hall, Memorial Arch, Encina Gym, Art Gallery, and Library (1919), circa 1905-1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hoover War Library: photographs of the model and postcards of the constructed Tower (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Apartment house and garage, 1926; 14 architectural drawing(s) (Box 3)
  - Pro Shop, Stanford University Golf Course, 1929; 2 architectural drawing(s) (Box 3)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Feb 12 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Feb 16 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Full Size Detail of Balconies (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Feb 02 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Feb 21 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Apr 21 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Feb 28 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Mar 30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Full Size Plan of Balcony, 1921 Mar 30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Full Size Detail of Balcony, 1921 Mar 30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Dining Rm, Clubrooms and Corridors, 1924 Apr 05 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Full Size Detail of Balconies At Side of Main Entrance, 1921 Apr (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Apr 21 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Details of Medium Cordova Title Roof, 1920 Apr 07 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building FSD of Club No. 1, Faculty Dining Rm and Office, 1920 Apr 17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Stairs North Stair Hall, 1921 Apr 13 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building FSD of Lounging Room, 1921 Apr 14 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Club Room and Corridors, 1921 Apr 15 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Apr 19 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Doors, 1921 Apr 21 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Exterior Wood Doors, 1921 Apr 22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Door to Trunk Room, 1921 Apr 25 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Details of Kitchen Cases, 1921 Apr 26 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building, 1921 Apr 05 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Radiator Layout, 1921 Apr 27 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Full Size Detail Kitchen Wing and Basement, 1921 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Building Trim of 2nd 3rd Floors, 1921 May 05 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union Detail of Finials at side of 3rd floor window over main entrance, 1921 May 04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Trim for Sash in Stair Wells, 1921 May 06 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Louvers in Gables of Stair Wings, 1921 May 04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Access Doors to Towers, 1921 May 07 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Trunk Lift Shaft, 1921 May 09 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Details of Cold Storage Rooms, 1921 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Head of Mantel Piece, 1921 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Cables, 1921 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Eaves of Main Roof, 1921 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Eaves of Arcades and Eaves for Roof of Coat Rooms, 1921 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Fire Place in Lounging Room, 1921 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Eaves of Kitchen Roof, 1921 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union URN, 1921 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Beams in Entrance Porch, 1921 May 14 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Vent in East Gable, 1921 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Urns Above Column at Main Entrance, 1921 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Main Entrance of Arcade (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Archivolt, 1921 May 01 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Letters on Arcade Entrance, 1921 Jun 13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Partition in Corridor Second Floor, 1921 Jun 30 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Alternate Trim in Corridors, 1921 Aug 29 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Window of Office, 1921 Oct (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Door Between Lounging Room into Corridor, 1921 Oct 21 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Window on Kitchen Porch, 1921 Nov 17 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Main Cornice Rear Elevation (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Bacteriological Lab. Tables (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Bacteriological Lab. Tables Plain Through Locker (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Window Details Door Details, 1920 Dec 01 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Belt Course 2nd Floor, 1921 Feb 05 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Belt Course Around 7th Story Roof, 1920 Dec 06 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Main Cornice (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Bay Windows Doors To Roof, 1920 Dec 14 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Full Size Roof Garden Sash, 1920 Dec 16 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Main Entrance Cornice and Pilaster, 1921 Feb (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Entrance Ground Floor, 1921 Feb 18 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Furred Reception Room, 1921 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Lobby Recept Room Corridor and Waiting Room, 1921 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Book Cases in Laboratory, 1921 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Assembly Room, 1921 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Assembly Room Part A, 1921 Feb 08 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Assembly Room Part B, 1921 Feb 08 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Section Through Foot Lights Stage in Assembly Room, 1921 Mar 25 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Stair and Elevator Lobby, 1921 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Mantel in Furred Reception Room, 1921 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Doors and Transom Lights (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Typical Details, 1921 Jan 25 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Detail of Marquise, 1920 Feb 08 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Inscription over Side Entrance, 1921 Mar 18 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Cases in Diatetics RM Kitchenette and Class Rooms, 1921 Feb 18 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Cornice at Baywindow full size, 1921 Mar 12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Assembly Hall Columns Stairs, 1921 Mar 23 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Medicine Cabinet, 1921 Jan 31 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Shower Rooms, 1921 Mar 07 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Threshold Main Entrance (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Full Size Section at "AA" (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Arch To Stair First Floor, 1921 Aug 25 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Nurses Home Full Size Sections Panels on Rear Wall of Stage, 1921 Dec 07 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Hospital FSD of Doors To Fire Escape Balconies, 1916 Oct 06 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Double Hung Windows Porch Doors, 1916 May 22 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Casement Antill Windows, 1916 May 25 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Drawings of Lighting Fixtures, 1917 Apr 04 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Ball (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Windows, 1916 Jun 10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Kinnear Rolling Doors, 1916 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Drawings of Lighting Fixtures, 1917 Apr 04 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Lamps (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Eg. 7012 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Exterior of Building (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital E 15269 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital E 1132 and E 18776 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Lamp (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital R 32580 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital 9439 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital R 29577 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital R 22849 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Wood Metal Doors Partition Lights Wainscot, 1916 May 12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Gardens in Basement 1st Floor, 1916 Oct 28 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital FSD Basement entrance, 1916 Oct 21 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Entrance to Treatment Room (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital FSD Door Keeper's Cage in Drive Way, 1916 Dec 09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Corridors in Basement, 1917 Jan 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Slabs in Supply Rooms, 1917 Jun 06 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Fume Cabinet in Laboratory (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Medicine Cabinets, 1916 Oct 27 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Marcquise, 1916 Oct 13 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Double Hung Sash, 1917 Apr 30 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Ceiling Lights, 1917 Jan 12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Desk in Nurses Station, 1917 Jan 09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Marquise Over Garden Entrance, 1916 Nov 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Louvre, 1917 Jan 04 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Mould At Top of Metal Roof (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Wood Shelves, 1917 Mar 21 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Wire Window Guards, 1917 Apr 06 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Bracket For Marquise, 1916 Oct 03 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Doors at End of Corridors (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Sills from Rooms To Balcony Porches, 1917 Apr 09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Cabinets (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Dutch Doors, 1916 Jan 15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Lights in Tile Partitions, 1916 Jan 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Showing Wood Runners Roller Box, 1917 Apr 10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Hose Reel Cabinets, 1916 Sept 28 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Spandrel, 1917 Jan 26 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital The Scale FSD of Dumb Waiters, 1917 Jan 17 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Marquise, 1916 Oct 03 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Details, 1917 Jan 19 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Utility Chamber Doors, 1917 Feb 15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Revision in Wood Bases, 1916 Mar 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Tables for Nurses Restroom, 1917 Oct 02 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Fire Escape, 1916 Oct 23 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Revised Elevators, 1916 Oct 09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Sub Basement Windows and Basement Base Course, 1916 Sep 13 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Driveway Entrance, 1916 Oct 21 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Galv Iron Cornice 5th Floor Line, 1916 Dec 07 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Fenestra Windows, Exterior Belt Courses, etc, 1916 Nov 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Exterior Architraves Cornices Belt Courses, 1916 Oct 25 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Hospital Detail Showing Arrangment of Water Closets, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)